{
    "id": "17b42c40f8c04de8a81f2ef99aa2fdc5",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Even though she is a graduate, she cannot put her ideas ......................... in English.",
            "description": "Put across = convey effectively",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "across",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8ebfcef54e6d403388e1fe5b8ed70070"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you want to lose weight, you must cut ............................ on your consumption of fast food.",
            "description": "To cut down is to reduce.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "down",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61494b27fc2546c381d184af7332a617"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have ............................... the meeting.",
            "description": "To put off is to postpone.",
            "answers": [
                "put up",
                "put on",
                "put off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "83009c608b354ddd89914fd4eec3b065"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .................................. after a prolonged battle with cancer.",
            "description": "To pass away is to die.",
            "answers": [
                "passed out",
                "passed away",
                "passed off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0da7aef952a642ec83fce22984cf668c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................ her grandmother.",
            "description": "Take after = resemble",
            "answers": [
                "takes on",
                "takes after",
                "takes out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d9312ee372324b81ba336bb7d917d4b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody can .................................... with him. He has such a short temper.",
            "description": "To get along is to have good relation with",
            "answers": [
                "get off",
                "get over",
                "get along"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c2a4b7c4c5ca40538f54fa842fd55743"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will get that job if you .............................. a word for me.",
            "description": "To put in a word is to recommend.",
            "answers": [
                "put up",
                "put in",
                "put out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9076eebf8b645f79b9b51f5f7af713a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should stop running me .................................",
            "description": "To run somebody down is to criticize them severely.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "out",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3342189fa9c540578c4a0edccf129d2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "They fought bravely but in the end they had to ...............................",
            "description": "To give in is to surrender.",
            "answers": [
                "give up",
                "give in",
                "give off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "83d36af2330a42cb9d996bcaa700e324"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ........................................ her emotions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gave out",
                "gave vent to",
                "gave off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c12b90090aed4bb5bfc125068930019d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The speaker was going to conclude his address but the audience wanted him to ................................ for another fifteen minutes.",
            "description": "To go on is to continue.",
            "answers": [
                "go on",
                "take on",
                "put on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "812636293dc0494cad619211bc007368"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn't .................................. what she said.",
            "description": "To figure out is to understand.",
            "answers": [
                "figure out",
                "make up",
                "take in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b76cec9b09524b51bc427d82f41e76a3"
        }
    ]
}